<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://drkellyann.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://drkellyann.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://drkellyann.com/collections/bestsellers.atom"/>
  <title>Dr. Kellyann</title>
  <updated>2024-12-09T14:35:21-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Dr. Kellyann</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/7279313649777</id>
    <published>2024-12-09T14:35:21-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-12-09T14:35:21-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://drkellyann.com/products/21-day-bone-broth-classic-chicken"/>
    <title>21-Day Bone Broth Diet Bundle</title>
    <s:type>Soups &amp; Broths</s:type>
    <s:vendor>DISK</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/Bone_Broth_-_Classic_Chicken_6_box_bundle_1.png?v=1737132358"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>DISK<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Soups &amp; Broths<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            159.96
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div class="s-description">
<h2>21-Day Bone Broth Bundle</h2>
<p>If you decided to do Dr. Kellyann's Bone Broth Diet you've come to the right place to get all the bone broth you'll need for your 21-day transformation.</p>
<h2>All the nutrition, none of the work.</h2>
</div>
<p>Dr. Kellyann’s Bone Broth takes all the hard work and guesswork out of getting the collagen-packed protein and nutrients you need to nourish your body, control hunger cravings, and even help smooth away wrinkles — without any cooking or prepping so you can breeze through your 21 days!<br></p>
<p>I want your journey toward a healthier lifestyle to be on YOUR terms. I want you to look and feel your best whenever and wherever you want. And my anytime/anywhere single-servings of collagen-rich bone broth are the easiest (and tastiest) way to get there.</p>
<p><span>Consuming 1-2 packets of Dr. Kellyann's Bone Broth per day aids in supporting gut health and is ideal for intermittent fasting, GLP-1 diets, and weight loss programs. It's rich in nutrients, contains 0 sugar, and is high in protein, making it great for diabetics, seniors, and those on carnivore or paleo diets. This delicious bone broth is excellent for recovery, boosting immunity, and supporting skin, hair and nail health.</span></p>
<p><span>We suggest trying it as a savory satisfying snack when fasting, a meal accompaniment, or as a wholesome soup base in your favorite recipes.</span><span class="c-message__edited_label" dir="ltr" data-sk="tooltip_parent" aria-describedby="sk-tooltip-135077" delay="300"> </span></p>
<div class="s-description">
<span style="color: #ff2a00;" data-mce-style="color: #ff2a00;"></span>This 21-Day Bone Broth Diet product bundle gives you all the bone broth you’ll need to be successful on your 21-Day Bone Broth Diet.<br><br>
<p>This bundle includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>10 boxes of Collagen Broth <meta charset="UTF-8"> <span data-mce-fragment="1">—</span> that's 70 packets of convenient bone broth to-go! </li>
</ul>
<h3>Bone Broth Benefits</h3>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">+ 16g of protein per serving<br data-mce-fragment="1">+ Only 70 calories and less than 1g of carbs<span> </span><br data-mce-fragment="1">+ Just 230mg of sodium per serving<br data-mce-fragment="1">+ No fat / No sugar / No cholesterol<br>+ Cage-free chicken<br>+ Slow-simmered for 8 hours<br>+ Includes 7 individual packets<br>+ Just add hot water and serve! </p>
<h3><b>Anytime, Anywhere Bone Broth</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Directions: Pour contents into bowl and add 8-12 oz. of boiling water. Stir until blended. Add your favorite spices for added flavor.</span></p>
<h3><b>How Can Bone Broth Support Your Health?</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When animal bones are slow-cooked, the marrow and connective tissues release health-supporting nutrients like vitamins, minerals, and collagen-packed protein. When you go through our 21-day plan, you can see benefits in many areas of your overall wellness.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These can include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Weight loss</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Skin, joint, and bone health</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hydration</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Digestion</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Metabolism</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sleep health</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The extra protein in the broth may give you more control over your appetite and reduce hunger cravings in between meals by keeping you feeling fuller for longer. The extra protein can also play a key role in helping you maintain muscle mass and support healthy blood sugar levels. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The animal bones also contain gelatin. When our bodies digest gelatin, it is deconstructed into amino acids like glycine, glutamine, and proline. These amino acids are then sent out to wherever the body needs them. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amino acids are the building blocks of proteins and can help support digestive health, natural collagen production, and a healthy metabolism. Glutamine and glycine can also help support the gut lining and your gut microbiome, which can, in turn, support your overall health.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our bone broths are full of supportive nutrients like:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Collagen</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vitamin D</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vitamin A </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vitamin K </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fatty acids</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Iron</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Zinc</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Phosphorus</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Calcium </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Potassium </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Magnesium </span></li>
</ul>
<p><b>Encourages Healthy Weight Loss</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bone broth is low in carbs, sugar, and calories, so it makes sense that, for many, it can help curb cravings and support weight loss goals. The benefits of losing weight are felt on the inside and the outside. When you start to look great, you may start to feel great, too!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You can easily incorporate Dr. Kellyann’s bone broth by substituting bone broth for caffeinated or sugary drinks, throwing one of our on-the-go packets in your gym bag, or using it as a base for your favorite soup. And of course, you can embark on our bone broth diet plan.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By drinking two servings of Dr. Kellyann’s delicious bone broth every day, you can get an extra 32 ounces of protein into your diet, which can help you feel fuller for longer. You can also combine the benefits of bone broth with diet methods like intermittent fasting and low-carb diets.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just make sure to save your cup of bone broth for a non-fasting day, as bone broth can break a fast.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you start replacing foods that are high in sugar and carbohydrates with clean foods that are high in protein, you can burn more calories and support your metabolism. The results can be amazing!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Plus, our beef and chicken bone broths work with both keto and paleo diets. And, while there are plenty of bone broth recipes that feature non-starchy vegetables and healthy fats (while avoiding artificial sweeteners or legumes),we prefer to enjoy bone broth as-is.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After all, when you’re drinking Dr. Kellyann Petrucci’s high-quality, grass-fed chicken or beef bone broth, why add anything at all?</span></p>
<p><b>Supports Younger-Looking Skin</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not only can the bone broth diet support your weight loss journey, but the collagen contained in each serving can help support skin health, as well. Unfortunately, one fact of life is that, as we age, our natural ability to produce collagen can diminish. This can even start as early as our 20s.   </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When collagen production starts to decline, that’s when we begin to notice things like sagging skin, hallowed areas around our eyes, and fine lines and wrinkles. The good news is that you can add some collagen back to your body by drinking bone broth.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over time, you may see improvements in the tone and texture of your skin. It may even help smoothen the appearance of cellulite. </span></p>
<p><b>Promotes Gut Health</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bone broth can also play an important role in your gut health. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The gut is also sometimes called the body’s second brain. It’s no wonder, then, that a happy gut can contribute to a happier state of being. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The nutrients, proteins, and amino acids contained in bone broth can help coat the lining of your gut and support healthy digestion. Specifically, the amino acids glutamine and glycine both play vital roles in the digestive system. </span></p>
<h3><b>How Else Can You Use Bone Broth?</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The gut is the epicenter of the body, and a healthy gut can support your overall wellness — so it’s time to start taking gut health seriously. A great way to take advantage of the benefits of bone broth is by using it as part of a detox to support your microbiome.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Try using Dr. Kellyann’s 5-Day-Cleanse &amp; Reset Kit to get harmful bacteria and toxins in check. This cleansing meal plan includes some of Dr. Kellyann’s favorite cleansing foods like Lemon Sips, Chocolate or Vanilla Super Smoothies, Super Berry Smoothies, and our Lemon Chicken Soup.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By pressing the restart button with a bone broth cleanse, you may be able to minimize uncomfortable bloating, digestive discomfort, and even skin concerns. The minerals and nutrients contained in bone broth can support your gut, while collagen can help you lose that stubborn belly fat.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fortunately, bone broth can fit in a wide range of diets. Those who are on a gluten-free or keto diet should be able to incorporate bone broth into their diet easily. Simply add some veggies, and you have a nutritious and diet-friendly soup that can help you feel full and look amazing.</span></p>
<p><span size="1" style="font-size: xx-small;" data-mce-style="font-size: xx-small;">California Prop 65 Warning</span></p>
<p><span size="1" style="font-size: xx-small;" data-mce-style="font-size: xx-small;"><meta charset="utf-8"> <img data-mce-fragment="1" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461" alt="" data-mce-src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461"> WARNING: Consuming the bone broth in this product can expose you to chemicals including lead which is known to the State of California to cause cancer and birth defects or other reproductive harm. For more information go to<span> </span><a href="http://www.p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food" target="_blank">p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food</a>.</span></p>
<div>✝<em>These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.</em>
</div>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p><!-- split --></p>
<p><img height="331" width="331" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/Bone_Broth_-_Nutrition_Facts-_CC.png?v=1723643951" alt=""></p>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>badge:trending</s:tag>
    <s:tag>bestseller</s:tag>
    <s:tag>bonebroth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>dairy-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>gluten-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>healthier_2019</s:tag>
    <s:tag>keto-friendly</s:tag>
    <s:tag>non-gmo</s:tag>
    <s:tag>paleo-friendly</s:tag>
    <s:tag>shipping_international</s:tag>
    <s:tag>soy-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-default</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-disabled</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/7279313649777</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">159.96</s:price>
      <s:sku>CBBDRK06</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6565263966321</id>
    <published>2024-06-17T13:22:10-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-06-17T13:22:10-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://drkellyann.com/products/lemon-sips"/>
    <title>Lemon Sips</title>
    <s:type>Lemon Sips</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Dr. Kellyann</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/DKA_LemonSips_Aluminum_rollover.png?v=1696438338"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Dr. Kellyann<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Lemon Sips<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            47.00 - 226.00
            <a href="https://drkellyann.com/products/lemon-sips">(3 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’ve tried my Cleanse &amp; Reset then you’ve already experienced the amazing health and beauty benefits of my Lemon Sips powdered drink mix. If you haven’t, let me tell you about some of the incredible things this nearly sugar-free, fat-free, citrusy-delicious drink can do for you and your skin.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By simply tantalizing your taste buds with one glass of natural Lemon Sips each day, you’ll soon discover that it:</span></p>
<ul data-mce-fragment="1">
<li style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Helps detoxify + flush toxins from your system</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Helps smooth skin and decrease skin dimpling</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Rehydrates and nourishes your skin </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Helps protect skin from UV damage</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">And, of course, quenches the strongest thirst!</li>
</ul>
<div class="s-description"> <br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The real magic ingredient in my Lemon Sips formula is SOD B® — a natural, antioxidant-rich extract derived from cantaloupe. Maybe you’ve read about some of the incredible results of this miraculous French body-shaping ingredient, and how it has shown to help smooth skin and skin dimpling around thighs (those “cottage cheeks”), help restore skin elasticity and resilience, protect against UV skin damage, and help shrink fat cells below the skin surface.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">SOD B® is an ingredient that can actually help smooth out skin folds when taken orally — not applied to the skin! As a matter of fact, a recent clinical study reported that just 40mg a day of SOD B® help smooth skin on thighs by up to 9.5% after 28 days, and up to 11.3% after 56 days.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lemon Sips is also a great way to enhance the slimming, nourishing, and beautifying effects of all my other products, thanks to its detoxifying and hydrating properties. And did I mention it’s super delicious?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Upgrade your H20 with Lemon Sips! And turn any plain ol’ glass of water into a refreshing, revitalizing, and rehydrating elixir of beautiful energy.</span></p>
<h6><strong>* For best results, consume within 1 hour of mixing. If making Lemon Sips with hot water, consume within 20 minutes of mixing.</strong></h6>
<p> </p>
</div>
<div class="p65-o">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1"></b><span size="1" style="font-size: xx-small;" data-mce-style="font-size: xx-small;">California Prop 65 Warning</span></p>
<p><span size="1" style="font-size: xx-small;" data-mce-style="font-size: xx-small;"><meta charset="utf-8"> <img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461" alt="" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461"> WARNING: Consuming this product can expose you to chemicals including lead which is known to the State of California to cause cancer and birth defects or other reproductive harm. For more information go to<span> </span><a href="http://www.p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food" target="_blank">p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food</a>.</span></p>
<div>✝<em>These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.</em>
</div>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p><span><!-- split --> </span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p> </p>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>bestseller</s:tag>
    <s:tag>lemon sips</s:tag>
    <s:tag>shipping_international</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-default</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-enabled</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Subscription</s:tag>
    <s:tag>trending</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Ygroup_lemonsips</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6565263966321</id>
      <title>1 Jar</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">47.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>LMSIPDRK01</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6565263966321</id>
      <title>3 Jars</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">120.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>LMSIPDRK03</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6565263966321</id>
      <title>6 Jars</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">226.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>LMSIPDRK06</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6962354913393</id>
    <published>2024-02-26T16:41:04-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-26T16:41:04-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://drkellyann.com/products/peri-menopause"/>
    <title>Dr. Kellyann &amp;ME Peri + Menopause</title>
    <s:type>Hormonal</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Dr. Kellyann</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/DKA_AndMe_Peri.jpg?v=1708659543"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Dr. Kellyann<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Hormonal<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            69.00 - 331.20
            <a href="https://drkellyann.com/products/peri-menopause">(4 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>badge:new</s:tag>
    <s:tag>bestseller</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6962354913393</id>
      <title>1 Pack</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>DKAMEPERMI01</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6962354913393</id>
      <title>2 Pack</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">129.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>DKAMEPERMI-1JAR-1PK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6962354913393</id>
      <title>3 Pack</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">175.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>DKAMEPERMI-1JAR-2PK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6962354913393</id>
      <title>6 Pack</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">331.20</s:price>
      <s:sku>DKAMEPERMI-1JAR-5PK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6576498212977</id>
    <published>2021-07-15T06:39:35-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-07-15T06:39:35-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://drkellyann.com/products/bellabiotics"/>
    <title>BellaBiotics</title>
    <s:type>BellaBiotics</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Dr. Kellyann</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/products/BellaBiotics.png?v=1679693118"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Dr. Kellyann<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>BellaBiotics<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            49.00 - 229.00
            <a href="https://drkellyann.com/products/bellabiotics">(4 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div class="s-description">
<h3><strong>The Science of Beautiful Skin</strong></h3>
</div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BellaBiotics combines two of today’s most cutting-edge cosmetic discoveries — Dermaval® and Korean Mint — and blends them with the proven beauty-boosting benefits of clinical-grade probiotics, nutrients, and essential vitamins.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By targeting your skin and gut microbiomes from a cellular level, BellaBiotics helps restore your skin’s elasticity, smooths out wrinkles and skin sagging, reduces blemishes, protects against ultraviolet damage from electronic devices, boosts your body’s collagen and elastin production, and even improves your digestive health — all from the inside out.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This revolutionary once-a-day capsule literally retrains your skin’s behavior, rebuilds your foundational beauty from its core, and restores your skin’s youthful resilience and glow.</span></p>
<div class="s-description">
<h3><strong><em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">BellaBiotics: The Science of Beautiful Skin</span></em></strong></h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Reduces appearance of wrinkles and fine lines</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Reduces the appearance of blemishes</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Helps repair and protect against UV skin damage</span></li>
<li>Promotes collagen and elastin production<br>
</li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Supports healthy gut and skin microbiomes</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Contains 30 mint-coated daily capsules</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span data-mce-fragment="1" style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">What’s the secret? There is no secret — it’s simple science. Your skin health is directly connected to your gut health. By nourishing your gut microbiome (your internal ecosystem), you can repair and improve your skin health from the inside out, naturally. And the longer you use BellaBiotics, the more long-term beauty and digestive benefits you will experience.</span> <br></p>
<h3><b>Beauty-Boosting Ingredients:</b></h3>
<p><b>Clinical-Grade Probiotics</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We included two potent strains — Lactobacillus paracasei + Lactococcus lactis (12 billion CFU) — specifically for their proven digestive support and skin-hydrating, -nourishing and -repairing properties.</span></p>
<p><b>Korean Mint</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This powerful and natural antioxidant has been shown to repair UV-induced wrinkle formations, reduce the appearance of fine lines, and keep skin plump and moisturized.</span></p>
<p><b> </b><b>Dermaval</b><b>®</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This all-natural blend of nine plant-based antioxidants builds up your beauty proteins, promotes skin elasticity, and supports your body’s production of skin-restoring collagen and elastin.</span></p>
<p><b> </b><b>Vitamin A</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vitamin A has been shown to stimulate the production of new skin cells and enhance your body’s own collagen production.</span></p>
<p><b> </b><b>Vitamin D</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vitamin D helps protect the skin, regulate its maintenance and health, and even prevents the buildup of dead cells on skin’s surface. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><b>Vitamin E</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vitamin E is essential for skin health and function, and constantly needs to be replenished due to depletion from UV light and sun exposure.  </span></p>
<p><b>DIRECTIONS:</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Take one capsule daily with food.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BellaBiotics (and refill packets) do not need to be refrigerated. However, there is no harm if you would like to keep them in a refrigerator until use. We recommend<b> storing in a cool, d</b><strong>ry</strong> place.</span></p>
<p><b>Ordering Information:</b></p>
<p><span>In order to keep our planet healthy and beautiful, we are cutting down on the use of plastic materials whenever possible. With this in mind:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<span>When you order a </span><b>1-month supply</b><span> of BellaBiotics, you will receive our beautiful collector’s jar filled with </span><b>30 capsules.</b>
</li>
<li>
<span>When you order a </span><b>3-month supply</b><span>, you will receive the collector’s jar (with 30 capsules) along with two refill packets (30 capsules each) for a total of </span><b>90 capsules</b><span>.</span>
</li>
<li>
<span>When you order a </span><b>6-month supply</b><span>, you will receive the collector’s jar (with 30 capsules) plus five refill packets (30 capsules each) for a total of </span><b>180 capsules</b><span>.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><b>Feed the jar!</b><span> Once your BellaBiotics jar is empty, </span><span>don’t throw it away</span><span>. Simply open one of the air-tight refill packets, pour contents into the jar, and keep sealed until you’re ready to use. This way, we’re all doing our part to protect our planet!</span></p>
<p><span>Sign up for our subscription option to ensure you never run out! </span>All subsequent BellaBiotics orders will be delivered as refill packets.</p>
<p> </p>
<div>
<div>✝<em>These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.</em>
</div>
</div>
<p> </p>
<p><!-- split --></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><em><strong><img height="622" width="374" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/Screen_Shot_2021-06-01_at_10.53.19_AM_480x480.png?v=1622570968" alt=""></strong></em></span></p>
<br>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>badge:back in stock</s:tag>
    <s:tag>bella biotics</s:tag>
    <s:tag>bestseller</s:tag>
    <s:tag>shipping_international</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-default</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-disabled</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6576498212977</id>
      <title>1 Month</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">49.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>BELLA-1JAR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6576498212977</id>
      <title>2 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">89.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>BELLA-1JAR-1PK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6576498212977</id>
      <title>3 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">129.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>BELLA-1JAR-2PK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/6576498212977</id>
      <title>6 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">229.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>BELLA-1JAR-5PK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/4638854971505</id>
    <published>2021-01-02T14:49:54-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-02T14:49:54-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://drkellyann.com/products/new-and-improved-v3-5-day-cleanse-and-reset-kit"/>
    <title>5-Day Cleanse and Reset Kit</title>
    <s:type>Nutrition Drinks &amp; Shakes</s:type>
    <s:vendor>DISK</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/products/DKA_CleanseKit_5Day_front.png?v=1696441215"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>DISK<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Nutrition Drinks &amp; Shakes<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            230.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div class="s-description">
<h2>
<b data-mce-fragment="1">Dr. Kellyann’s 5-Day Cleanse &amp; Reset</b><br>
</h2>
</div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Are you ready to restore, renew, and re-energize your whole body with my 5-Day Cleanse &amp; Reset kit?</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">I’ve improved my original Green Smoothie. It still has detoxifying greens and a hint of sweetness from berries but now you get to choose whether you want it in chocolate or vanilla. And, I've added<span> </span><strong>whey protein isolate</strong><span> </span>to the hydrolyzed collagen for an improved amino acid and antioxidant profile. </p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Also, many of you told me you wanted another warm meal option so I've included a bone broth for lunch.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">And probably my favorite improvement is in the Lemon Sips. I supercharged my Lemon Sips with a new melon concentrate called SOD B<meta content="text/html; charset=utf-8" http-equiv="content-type"><span data-mce-fragment="1">®</span>. This all-natural extract has been clinically shown to smooth away cellulite by shrinking fat cells hiding just below the skin. </p>
<div class="s-description">
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">The results: You’ll look and feel better, you’ll have improved gut health with less bloating, your skin will look and feel healthier, and your hair and nails will grow stronger and more lustrous. Plus, your bones and joints will be supported with all sorts of reparative nutrients.</span></p>
<p><b>Look &amp; Feel Younger</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Cleanse &amp; Reset is loaded with hundreds of the highest quality vitamins, minerals, nutrients plus a variety of proteins to supersaturate your body with the most intense nutrition you've ever experienced … and will have you looking and feeling great.</span></p>
<p><b>Better Gut Health</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Cleanse &amp; Reset helps your digestive system repair the damage done by toxins, to reduce bloating and gas. You’ll also get the antioxidants and amino acids your body needs to repair an overworked gut, prevent heartburn, and nourish your gut lining to help with issues like leaky gut syndrome.</span></p>
<p><b>Firmer, Healthier Skin</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Toxins will be flushed out, and those unwanted signs of aging will start to vanish. My kit is rich in protein-packed collagen, for a daily dose of healthy-fat nutrients that’ll tighten and condition your skin and help lessen lines and wrinkles. I’ve also supercharged my Lemon Sips with a new melon concentrate called SOD B. This all-natural extract has been clinically shown to smooth away cellulite by shrinking fat cells hiding just below the skin. </span></p>
<p><b>Weight Loss</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">The best way to slim down quickly is by cleansing. When you rid your body of toxins and inflammation while staying full on delicious soups and smoothies, shedding excess weight becomes a breeze. My new “lactose-free” whey protein isolate in my Super Chocolate Smoothies is a nutritional powerhouse that builds lean muscle and offers added support for slimming down. Plus, the “healthy fat” from all of my collagen-rich meals melts away belly fat … because healthy fats actually burn fat.</span></p>
<p><b>Whole-Body Health</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">The health benefits of saturating yourself with the essential vitamins and nutrients in my cleanse go well beyond the beautifying results. You’ll also feel full and satisfied, your system will flush out those unhealthy toxins, you’ll feel more energetic during the day, and your body will be flushed with lean muscle-building protein.</span></p>
<p><b>Lustrous Hair &amp; Nails</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">With a blend of antioxidants, minerals, and collagen, my protein-rich cleanse will coat your cells with the nutrients your body is craving. You’ll find your nails turning stronger and smoother, follicles becoming more nourished, and hair growing thicker, stronger, and more radiant.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b>This 5-Day Kit includes:</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">15 Lemon Sips</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">5 Super Chocolate Smoothies -OR- 5 Super Vanilla Smoothies </span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">5 Bone Broths</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">5 Super Berry Smoothies</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">5 Lemon Chicken Soups</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">REFRESH</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Start your morning with a refreshing glass of <strong>Lemon Sip</strong> to flush out toxins, rehydrate your body, and energize your mind. Two more Lemon Sips will keep you awake and alert all day long.</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">REVITALIZE</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">For breakfast, revitalize your entire system with a mouthwatering </span><b data-mce-fragment="1">Super Chocolate or Vanilla Smoothie</b><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">. It’s loaded with protein, collagen, greens, and berries for a whole-body pick-me-up. </span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">REJUVENATE</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Sip on a savory bowl of low-calorie </span><b data-mce-fragment="1">Bone Broth</b><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;"> for lunch. It’s packed with protein and nutrients to nourish your body, support gut health, rejuvenate skin cells, and satisfy hunger cravings. </span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">RESET</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Treat your taste-buds to a </span><b data-mce-fragment="1">Super Berry Smoothie</b><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;"> midday. It’s rich in antioxidants and fat-burning superfoods to help your body fight free-radicals, boost energy, and keep aging at bay. </span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">RESTORE</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Our </span><b data-mce-fragment="1">Lemon Chicken Soup</b><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;"> is the cornerstone of your detox program. Enjoy it at dinnertime so the nutrients can work their magic through the night, and you can wake up feeling refreshed and restored. </span></p>
<p><span size="1" style="font-size: xx-small;" data-mce-style="font-size: xx-small;">California Prop 65 Warning</span></p>
<p><span size="1" style="font-size: xx-small;" data-mce-style="font-size: xx-small;"><meta charset="utf-8"> <img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461" alt="" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461"> WARNING: Consuming the bone broth in this product can expose you to chemicals including lead which is known to the State of California to cause cancer and birth defects or other reproductive harm. For more information go to<span> </span><a href="http://www.p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food" data-mce-href="http://www.p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food" target="_blank">p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food</a>.</span></p>
<div>✝<em>These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.</em>
</div>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p><!-- split --></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">LEMON SIP</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Lemon powder, Natural flavor, Stevia leaf extract, Melon juice concentrate (SOD B</span><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">®</span><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">)</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">SUPER CHOCOLATE SMOOTHIE*</b></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Dr. Kellyann Protein Complex [Whey Protein Isolate(WPI), Collagen Peptide], Prebiotic complex [Inulin, Konjac root, Xylooligosaccharides], Cocoa powder, Natural flavors, Medium chain triglycerides (MCT), Xanthan gum, Flaxseed, Sea salt, Beet root, Spirulina, Monk fruit extract, Chia seed, Stevia leaf extract, Steviol glycoside, Watercress herb, Collard, Cabbage, Spinach, Lactase, Broccoli, Alfalfa, Blueberry, Celery, Dandelion, Kale, Kelp</span></p>
<p><b>SUPER VANILLA SMOOTHIE*</b></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Dr. Kellyann Protein Complex [Whey Protein Isolate(WPI), Collagen Peptide], Prebiotic complex [Inulin, Konjac root, Xylooligosaccharides], Natural flavors, Medium chain triglycerides (MCT), Xanthan gum, Flaxseed, Beet root, Sea salt, Spirulina, Monk fruit extract, Chia seed, Stevia leaf extract, Steviol glycoside, Watercress herb, Collard, Cabbage, Spinach, Lactase, Broccoli, Alfalfa, Blueberry, Celery, Dandelion, Kale, Kelp</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">BONE BROTH</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Chicken bone broth powder, Natural flavors, Grass-fed bovine hydrolyzed collagen, Salt, Cauliflower powder, Minced green onion, Reishi mushroom powder, Turmeric extract</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">SUPER BERRY SMOOTHIE</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Grass-fed bovine hydrolyzed collagen, Medium chain triglycerides (MCT), Prebiotic fiber (from konjac root), Natural berries flavor, Citric acid, Lemon, Organic Strawberry, Cherry, Apple, Blueberry, Orange, Cranberry, Stevia leaf extract, Blackberry, Raspberry, Grape, Peach, Black currant, Monk fruit extract, Black chokeberry, Plum, Apricot, Pomegranate extract, Elderberry</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">LEMON CHICKEN SOUP</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Medium chain triglycerides (MCT), Hydrolyzed collagen, Chicken broth, Chicken fat, Cauliflower, Natural flavors, Garlic, Onion, Konjac root, Turmeric, Salt, Olive oil, Acacia gum, Tomato, Collard greens, Minced green onion, Carrot, Celery, Celery fragments, Citric acid, Green onion fragments, Green bell pepper, Kale fragments, Spinach fragments, Tomato fragments, Apple cider vinegar, Black pepper, Parsley, Sage, Rosemary extract, Thyme</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">*<em><strong>Depending on the flavor you choose, your Cleanse &amp; Reset Kit will contain either 1 Super Chocolate Smoothie OR 1 Super Vanilla Smoothie.</strong></em></span></p>
<div>
<div>✝<em>These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.</em>
</div>
</div>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>#generalfunnel</s:tag>
    <s:tag>badge:trending</s:tag>
    <s:tag>bestseller</s:tag>
    <s:tag>gluten-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>non-gmo</s:tag>
    <s:tag>paleo-friendly</s:tag>
    <s:tag>shipping_international</s:tag>
    <s:tag>soy-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-default</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-disabled</s:tag>
    <s:tag>trending</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/4638854971505</id>
      <title>Chocolate</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">230.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>5DCRK-CHOCV3</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1134</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/4638854971505</id>
      <title>Vanilla</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">230.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>5DCRK-VANV3</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1134</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/4638933123185</id>
    <published>2021-01-02T14:46:26-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-02T14:46:26-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://drkellyann.com/products/3-day-cleanse-and-reset-kit-improved"/>
    <title>3-Day Cleanse and Reset Kit</title>
    <s:type>Nutrition Drinks &amp; Shakes</s:type>
    <s:vendor>DISK</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/products/DKA_CleanseKit_3Day_front.png?v=1696441217"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>DISK<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Nutrition Drinks &amp; Shakes<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            141.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div class="s-description">
<h2>
<strong><b data-mce-fragment="1">Dr. Kellyann’s 3-Day Cleanse &amp; Reset</b></strong><br>
</h2>
</div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Are you ready to restore, renew, and re-energize your whole body with my 3-Day Cleanse &amp; Reset kit?</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">I’ve improved my original Green Smoothie. It still has detoxifying greens and a hint of sweetness from berries but now you get to choose whether you want it in chocolate or vanilla. And, I've added<span> </span><strong>whey protein isolate</strong><span> </span>to the hydrolyzed collagen for an improved amino acid and antioxidant profile. </p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Also, many of you told me you wanted another warm meal option so I've included a bone broth for lunch.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">And probably my favorite improvement is in the Lemon Sips. I supercharged my Lemon Sips with a new melon concentrate called SOD B<meta content="text/html; charset=utf-8" http-equiv="content-type"><span data-mce-fragment="1">®</span>. This all-natural extract has been clinically shown to smooth away cellulite by shrinking fat cells hiding just below the skin. </p>
<div class="s-description">
<p><b>Look &amp; Feel Younger</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleanse &amp; Reset is loaded with hundreds of the highest quality vitamins, minerals, nutrients plus a variety of proteins to supersaturate your body with the most intense nutrition you've ever experienced … and will have you looking and feeling great.</span></p>
<p><b>Better Gut Health</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleanse &amp; Reset helps your digestive system repair the damage done by toxins, to reduce bloating and gas. You’ll also get the antioxidants and amino acids your body needs to repair an overworked gut, prevent heartburn, and nourish your gut lining to help with issues like leaky gut syndrome.</span></p>
<p><b>Firmer, Healthier Skin</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Toxins will be flushed out, and those unwanted signs of aging will start to vanish. My kit is rich in protein-packed collagen, for a daily dose of healthy-fat nutrients that’ll tighten and condition your skin and help lessen lines and wrinkles. I’ve also supercharged my Lemon Sips with a new melon concentrate called SOD B. This all-natural extract has been clinically shown to smooth away cellulite by shrinking fat cells hiding just below the skin. </span></p>
<p><b>Weight Loss</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The best way to slim down quickly is by cleansing. When you rid your body of toxins and inflammation while staying full on delicious soups and smoothies, shedding excess weight becomes a breeze. My new “lactose-free” whey protein isolate in my Super Chocolate Smoothies is a nutritional powerhouse that builds lean muscle and offers added support for slimming down. Plus, the “healthy fat” from all of my collagen-rich meals melts away belly fat … because healthy fats actually burn fat.</span></p>
<p><b>Whole-Body Health</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The health benefits of saturating yourself with the essential vitamins and nutrients in my cleanse go well beyond the beautifying results. You’ll also feel full and satisfied, your system will flush out those unhealthy toxins, you’ll feel more energetic during the day, and your body will be flushed with lean muscle-building protein.</span></p>
<p><b>Lustrous Hair &amp; Nails</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With a blend of antioxidants, minerals, and collagen, my protein-rich cleanse will coat your cells with the nutrients your body is craving. You’ll find your nails turning stronger and smoother, follicles becoming more nourished, and hair growing thicker, stronger, and more radiant.</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">Here’s What You’ll Get in the Kit: </b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">9 Lemon Sips</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">3 Super Chocolate Smoothies -OR- 3 Super Vanilla Smoothies </span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">3 Bone Broths</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">3 Super Berry Smoothies</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">3 Lemon Chicken Soups</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">REFRESH</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Start your morning with a glass of refreshing </span><b data-mce-fragment="1">Lemon Sip</b><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;"> to flush out toxins, rehydrate your body, and energize your mind. Two more Lemon Sips will keep you awake and alert all day long. </span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">REVITALIZE</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">For breakfast, revitalize your entire system with a mouthwatering </span><b data-mce-fragment="1">Super Chocolate or Vanilla Smoothie </b><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">. It’s loaded with protein, collagen, greens, and berries for a whole-body pick-me-up. </span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">REJUVENATE</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Sip on a savory bowl of low-calorie </span><b data-mce-fragment="1">Bone Broth</b><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;"> for lunch. It’s packed with protein and nutrients to nourish your body, support gut health, rejuvenate skin cells, and satisfy hunger cravings. </span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">RESET</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Treat your taste-buds to a </span><b data-mce-fragment="1">Super Berry Smoothie</b><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;"> midday. It’s rich in antioxidants and fat-burning superfoods to help your body fight free-radicals, boost energy, and keep aging at bay. </span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">RESTORE</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Our </span><b data-mce-fragment="1">Lemon Chicken Soup</b><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;"> is the cornerstone of your detox program. Enjoy it at dinnertime so the nutrients can work their magic through the night, and you can wake up feeling refreshed and restored.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;"></span><span style="font-size: xx-small;" size="1" data-mce-style="font-size: xx-small;">California Prop 65 Warning</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: xx-small;" size="1" data-mce-style="font-size: xx-small;"><meta charset="utf-8"> <img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461"> WARNING: Consuming the bone broth in this product can expose you to chemicals including lead which is known to the State of California to cause cancer and birth defects or other reproductive harm. For more information go to<span> </span><a href="http://www.p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food" target="_blank">p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food</a>.</span></p>
<div>✝<em>These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.</em>
</div>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p><!-- split --></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">LEMON SIP</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Lemon powder, Natural flavor, Stevia leaf extract, Melon juice concentrate (SOD B</span><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">®</span><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">)</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">SUPER CHOCOLATE SMOOTHIE*</b></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Dr. Kellyann Protein Complex [Whey Protein Isolate(WPI), Collagen Peptide], Prebiotic complex [Inulin, Konjac root, Xylooligosaccharides], Cocoa powder, Natural flavors, Medium chain triglycerides (MCT), Xanthan gum, Flaxseed, Sea salt, Beet root, Spirulina, Monk fruit extract, Chia seed, Stevia leaf extract, Steviol glycoside, Watercress herb, Collard, Cabbage, Spinach, Lactase, Broccoli, Alfalfa, Blueberry, Celery, Dandelion, Kale, Kelp</span></p>
<p><b>SUPER VANILLA SMOOTHIE*</b></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Dr. Kellyann Protein Complex [Whey Protein Isolate(WPI), Collagen Peptide], Prebiotic complex [Inulin, Konjac root, Xylooligosaccharides], Natural flavors, Medium chain triglycerides (MCT), Xanthan gum, Flaxseed, Beet root, Sea salt, Spirulina, Monk fruit extract, Chia seed, Stevia leaf extract, Steviol glycoside, Watercress herb, Collard, Cabbage, Spinach, Lactase, Broccoli, Alfalfa, Blueberry, Celery, Dandelion, Kale, Kelp</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">BONE BROTH</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Chicken bone broth powder, Natural flavors, Grass-fed bovine hydrolyzed collagen, Salt, Cauliflower powder, Minced green onion, Reishi mushroom powder, Turmeric extract</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">SUPER BERRY SMOOTHIE</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Grass-fed bovine hydrolyzed collagen, Medium chain triglycerides (MCT), Prebiotic fiber (from konjac root), Natural berries flavor, Citric acid, Lemon, Organic Strawberry, Cherry, Apple, Blueberry, Orange, Cranberry, Stevia leaf extract, Blackberry, Raspberry, Grape, Peach, Black currant, Monk fruit extract, Black chokeberry, Plum, Apricot, Pomegranate extract, Elderberry</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">LEMON CHICKEN SOUP</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Medium chain triglycerides (MCT), Hydrolyzed collagen, Chicken broth, Chicken fat, Cauliflower, Natural flavors, Garlic, Onion, Konjac root, Turmeric, Salt, Olive oil, Acacia gum, Tomato, Collard greens, Minced green onion, Carrot, Celery, Celery fragments, Citric acid, Green onion fragments, Green bell pepper, Kale fragments, Spinach fragments, Tomato fragments, Apple cider vinegar, Black pepper, Parsley, Sage, Rosemary extract, Thyme</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">*<em><strong>Depending on the flavor you choose, your Cleanse &amp; Reset Kit will contain either 1 Super Chocolate Smoothie OR 1 Super Vanilla Smoothie.</strong></em></span></p>
<div>
<div>✝<em>These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.</em>
</div>
</div>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>#generalfunnel</s:tag>
    <s:tag>bestseller</s:tag>
    <s:tag>gluten-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>non-gmo</s:tag>
    <s:tag>paleo-friendly</s:tag>
    <s:tag>shipping_international</s:tag>
    <s:tag>soy-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-default</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-disabled</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/4638933123185</id>
      <title>Chocolate</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">141.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>3DCRK-CHOCV3</s:sku>
      <s:grams>680</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/4638933123185</id>
      <title>Vanilla</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">141.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>3DCRK-VANV3</s:sku>
      <s:grams>680</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/4627081822321</id>
    <published>2020-12-08T10:39:41-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-12-08T10:39:41-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://drkellyann.com/products/dr-kellyanns-bone-broth-1"/>
    <title>Classic Chicken Bone Broth</title>
    <s:type>Soups &amp; Broths</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Dr. Kellyann</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/Bone_Broth_-_Classic_Chicken_-1_1a9a7e62-8234-44a7-bac9-43678aeb0263.png?v=1737132540"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Dr. Kellyann<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Soups &amp; Broths<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            62.00 - 159.96
            <a href="https://drkellyann.com/products/dr-kellyanns-bone-broth-1">(3 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><h2 class="s-title">Classic Chicken Bone Broth</h2>
<p style="font-size: 1.5em;" class="s-title"><span style="color: #ff2a00;"></span><strong>Healthy. Delicious. And Oh So Easy.</strong></p>
<p><span>Dr. Kellyann's Bone Broth is crafted with one goal in mind: to deliver powerful nourishment to your brain and body in convenient, easy-to-prepare, on-the-go servings.</span><span></span><i data-stringify-type="italic"><span> </span></i></p>
<p><span>Consuming 1-2 packets of Dr. Kellyann's Bone Broth per day aids in supporting gut health and is ideal for intermittent fasting, GLP-1 diets, and weight loss programs. It's rich in nutrients, contains 0 sugar, and is high in protein, making it great for diabetics, seniors, and those on carnivore or paleo diets. This delicious bone broth is excellent for recovery, boosting immunity, and supporting skin, hair and nail health.</span></p>
<p><span>We suggest trying it as a savory satisfying snack, meal accompaniment, or wholesome soup base in your favorite recipes.</span><span aria-describedby="sk-tooltip-135077" data-sk="tooltip_parent" dir="ltr" class="c-message__edited_label" delay="300"> </span></p>
<div class="s-description">
<h3>Bone Broth Benefits</h3>
<p><meta charset="UTF-8"><span data-mce-fragment="1">+ 16g of protein per serving </span><br data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">+ Only 70 calories and less than 1g of carbs </span><br data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">+ Just 230mg of sodium per serving</span><br data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">+ </span><span data-mce-fragment="1">No fat / No sugar / No cholesterol<br></span>+ C<span data-mce-fragment="1">age-free chicken</span><br>+ Slow-simmered for 8 hours<br data-mce-fragment="1">+ Includes 7 individual packets<br data-mce-fragment="1">+ Just add hot water and serve!</p>
<h2>Live the Bone Broth Lifestyle </h2>
<p>Sipping on two cups of bone broth a day along with following a Paleo-based diet is the foundation of my bestselling book <a title="Dr. Kellyann's Bone Broth Diet" href="https://drkellyann.com/pages/bone-broth-diet" target="_blank"><em>Dr. Kellyann's Bone Broth Diet</em></a>.</p>
<p>Ordering is super simple. See what consuming this ancient superfood can do for you.</p>
<p><strong>Order 2 Boxes</strong>/14 packets for 2 cups of bone broth a day for one week.</p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8"><span data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>Order 4 Boxes</strong>/28 packets for 2 cups of bone broth a day for two weeks.</span></p>
<p><meta charset="utf-8"><span data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>Order 6 Boxes</strong>/42 packets for 2 cups of bone broth a day for three weeks.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<h2>Added BONUS</h2>
<p>With each order of my powdered Bone Broth you'll receive a <strong>digital lifestyle guide</strong> that gives you:</p>
<ul>
<li>Guide to maximizing your results</li>
<li>Meal plan guidelines</li>
<li>Portion guidelines</li>
<li>Shopping list of recommended "Yes" foods</li>
<li>Sample recipes<br>
</li>
<li>Exercise tips</li>
<li>and answers to common FAQs</li>
</ul>
<p> My Bone Broth Diet revolutionized the world of healthy, protein-rich home cuisine. Now, my Bone Broth on-the-go packets make it even easier to get the essential nutrients you need to nourish and repair your whole body — without the cooking or prepping.</p>
<p>I want your journey toward a healthier lifestyle to be on YOUR terms. I want you to look and feel your best whenever and wherever you want. And my anytime/anywhere single-servings of collagen-rich bone broth are the easiest (and tastiest) way to get there.</p>
<h2>Anytime, Anywhere Bone Broth</h2>
<p>Directions: Pour contents into bowl and add 8-12 oz. of boiling water. Stir until blended. Add your favorite spices for added flavor.</p>
<h3><b>How Do We Make Our Bone Broth?</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Making bone broth is the same for both liquid and powdered forms — except for the final step. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bone broth is made by simmering animal bones, connective tissues, and cartilage with a combination of apple cider vinegar, savory herbs, and spices in a slow cooker. Bovine bones and tissues are used for beef bone broth, while whole chicken feet, beaks, bones, and tissues are used to make chicken bone broth. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These are then simmered on a stovetop for a total cook time of over six hours.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After the slow-cooking process is complete, the broth becomes a gelatinous and nutrient-rich superfood. To make our best-selling bone broth powder, this “liquid gold” is then dehydrated into a powder.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dr. Kellyann only uses the bones of hormone-free, grass-fed bovine that hail from Germany and Brazil to make her hydrolyzed collagen powder. Dr. Kellyann’s hydrolyzed collagen is packed full of amino acids that are easy for the body to absorb. These amino acids can help support collagen and protein production in the body. </span></p>
<h3><b>How Can Bone Broth Benefit Your Health?</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You may know of bone broth as a safe and effective tool to help with weight loss, but there are many other benefits of bone broth, as well.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For instance, Dr. Kellyann’s Classic Chicken Bone Broth has 16 grams of added protein in each serving. That protein can help fuel your body and keep you feeling fuller for longer. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It also contains zero sugars, fats, or cholesterol and is also low in calories, carbohydrates, and saturated fat. This means it pairs perfectly with many weight loss programs and diets, including keto and paleo diets.   </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 15 to 16 grams of hydrolyzed collagen contained in each Classic Chicken Bone Broth packet can help smooth the appearance of fine lines and wrinkles, as well as minimize the effects of sagging skin.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our bodies naturally produce collagen, but as we age, collagen production can slow down. Eating foods that contain collagen and collagen-supporting amino acids is a great way to begin supporting your natural collagen production and skin elasticity.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bone broth is also rich in vitamins and minerals like calcium, potassium, magnesium, and collagen, thanks to the marrow bones used in bone broth recipes. This nutritious blend of minerals can help support gut health, weight loss, skin health, and overall wellness.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amino acids, like glutamine and glycine, can help support your gut microbiome. They may also help support new cell growth, the health of your gut lining, and overall digestion by helping to break down fats more thoroughly. </span></p>
<h3><b>What Recipes Can You Cook With Bone Broth?</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bone broth is a versatile blank canvas for a myriad of recipes. While we love drinking bone broth on its own, it’s also a wonderful base for gluten-free stew and soup recipes.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of our favorite ways to incorporate bone broth into a weeknight meal is by combining it with fresh veggies to make a hearty pho. Simply combine some veggies into a large pot or a crock pot, along with our bone broth, peppercorns, sea salt, bay leaves, and aromatic herbs, and cook on high heat. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Add in some freshly cooked chicken and some rice noodles, and there you have it! This easy recipe is a great way to use bone broth without adding unnecessary prep time. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you have some leftover bones laying around, you can add those, some water, and some aromatic herbs to a stock pot, instant pot, or pressure cooker to make a batch of bone broth at home. Or, you can save a trip to the grocery store by using Dr. Kellyann’s powdered bone broth.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Simply add this bone broth to any recipe that calls for liquid bone broth by dissolving one packet in eight ounces of hot water. Cut your total time for any broth-based recipe with this one simple trick!</span></p>
</div>
<div class="p65-o">
<p><span style="font-size: xx-small;" size="1" data-mce-style="font-size: xx-small;">California Prop 65 Warning</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: xx-small;" size="1" data-mce-style="font-size: xx-small;"><meta charset="utf-8"> <img data-mce-fragment="1" alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461" data-mce-src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461"> WARNING: Consuming the bone broth in this product can expose you to chemicals including lead which is known to the State of California to cause cancer and birth defects or other reproductive harm. For more information go to<span> </span><a href="http://www.p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food" target="_blank">p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food</a>.</span></p>
<div>✝<em>These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.</em>
</div>
</div>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p><span><span><!-- split --></span></span></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/Homestyle_BB_3_2022_480x480.png?v=1646077802"></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>bestseller</s:tag>
    <s:tag>bonebroth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>broth-selector</s:tag>
    <s:tag>dairy-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>gluten-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>grass-fed</s:tag>
    <s:tag>keto-friendly</s:tag>
    <s:tag>non-gmo</s:tag>
    <s:tag>paleo-friendly</s:tag>
    <s:tag>shipping_international</s:tag>
    <s:tag>size-based-image</s:tag>
    <s:tag>soy-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-default</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-disabled</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Subscription</s:tag>
    <s:tag>trending</s:tag>
    <s:tag>YGroup_homestyle</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/4627081822321</id>
      <title>2 Boxes</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">62.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>CBDRK02</s:sku>
      <s:grams>272</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/4627081822321</id>
      <title>4 Boxes</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">109.12</s:price>
      <s:sku>CBDRK04</s:sku>
      <s:grams>544</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/4627081822321</id>
      <title>6 Boxes</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">159.96</s:price>
      <s:sku>CBDRK06</s:sku>
      <s:grams>816</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/2608979116145</id>
    <published>2019-05-23T16:21:22-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-23T16:21:22-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://drkellyann.com/products/collagen-peptides-unflavored"/>
    <title>Collagen Peptides</title>
    <s:type>Nutrition Drinks &amp; Shakes</s:type>
    <s:vendor>DISK</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/DKA_Collagen_Peptides_front.png?v=1726502583"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>DISK<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Nutrition Drinks &amp; Shakes<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            45.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><h2 class="s-title">Collagen Peptides<br>
</h2>
<div>
<p><span>If you want to supplement your diet with collagen to help your skin and soft tissues maintain their strength and elasticity, you need my flavorless collagen peptide powder. Due to its flavorless nature, you can add this powder to any and all of your favorite drinks or dishes. Not only will it help you keep your skin and soft tissue healthy, it can also help you boost your daily protein intake.</span></p>
<div class="p65-o">
<p>All of my collagen products are highly concentrated and made from pure beef protein that is produced through a proprietary process to make it easily digestible. This is important because the easier it is for your body to digest, the more energy and nutritional value you gain from every scoop.</p>
<h2 class="s-title"><br></h2>
<p><span> </span><strong><span>How Collagen can help you stay healthy:</span></strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<span></span> <span>Improve joint comfort</span>
</li>
<li>
<span></span> <span>Promote hair thickness</span>
</li>
<li>
<span></span> <span>Support healthy blood sugar levels</span>
</li>
<li>
<span></span> <span>Support healthy skin</span>
</li>
<li>
<span></span> <span>Support gut health</span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span>My flavorless collagen peptides also pairs well with my Bone Broth Diet and 10 Day Belly Slimdown. All of my collagen protein is clean and dietary friendly.</span></p>
<p><strong><span>Healthy and Safe Collagen:</span></strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<span></span> <span>Grass-Fed Collagen Protein</span>
</li>
<li>
<span></span> <span>Keto-Friendly</span>
</li>
<li>
<span></span> <span>Paleo-Friendly</span>
</li>
<li>
<span></span> <span>Non-GMO</span>
</li>
<li>
<span></span> <span>Dairy-Free</span>
</li>
<li>
<span></span> <span>Soy Free</span>
</li>
</ul>
<h3><b>What Is Collagen?</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are 28 identified </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">types of collagen proteins</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in the human body. Of these, there are five that are considered the most important. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Type I</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> collagen is the most plentiful protein found in the human body. It acts as a fibrous connector inside </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">connective tissues</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, holding </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">ligaments</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, tendons, cartilage, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">muscle mass</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and bones together. It can support </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">skin elasticity</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and is responsible for maintaining a youthful appearance.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">type II</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> collagen can support </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">joint health</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. This natural collagen can lubricate your </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">ligaments</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and tendons, keeping your joints malleable and springy. A healthy level of </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">collagen synthesis</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in the body can provide </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">joint support</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and a </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">decline</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">collagen production</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> can result in </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">joint pain</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and other discomforts.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Collagen can also help support </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">gut health</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. When collagen is digested in the gut, it is broken down into </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">essential amino acids</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amino acids</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> are considered to be “the </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">building blocks</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">” of all proteins in the body and are used in the production of new </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">collagen proteins</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">amino acids</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> glutamine and glycine can also play important roles in our </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">wellness</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by helping to detox toxins from our guts and supporting a balanced gut microbiome. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amino acids</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> can also help support the production of additional stomach acid, which can help in the breakdown of fats in the digestive system.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unfortunately, our natural </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">collagen production</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> begins to </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">decline</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> as we mature, sometimes starting as early as our late twenties. When this begins, we may start to notice an increase in digestive discomfort, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">joint pain</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, fine lines, and wrinkles.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To support our bodies through this transition, it is important to consume </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">high-quality</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> foods or </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">collagen supplements</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that contain </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">hydrolyzed collagen</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> or </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">collagen peptides</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<h3>
<b>How Can You Use </b><b>Collagen Protein</b><b>?</b>
</h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dr. Kellyann makes collagen </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">accessibility</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> a breeze with her </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">multi-collagen protein</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">dietary supplements</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Reaping the </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">health benefits of collagen</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is easy as adding a scoop of this </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">collagen peptide powder</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to your </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">morning coffee</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> or </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">smoothie</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Plus, our supplements are made with </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">grass-fed</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">bovine collagen</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, so you can rest assured you’re getting the highest-quality ingredients.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dr. Kellyann’s </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unflavored</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">Collagen Peptides</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, along with her other </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">collagen protein powder</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> supplements, are easy and stress-free ways to increase your collagen intake.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">All of Dr. Kellyann’s products are </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">NON-GMO</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, contain no artificial </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">sweeteners</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, are low in </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">carbs</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and many are also compatible with </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">keto</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">paleo</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">gluten-free</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> diets. If you have any preexisting medical concerns, make sure to speak with your primary </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">healthcare</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> provider before adding any supplements to your diet. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For extra protein power, try combining a </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">serving size</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> of this </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">collagen powder</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with your favorite </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">smoothie</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and then finish out your day with a </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">soup</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> made with our </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">bone broth</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Supporting your </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">skin health</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> has never been easier!</span></p>
<div>✝<em>These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.</em>
</div>
<p> </p>
</div>
<p><!-- split --> <img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/DKA_Peptide_NFP_60_Servigns_480x480.png?v=1600875899" alt="" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/DKA_Peptide_NFP_60_Servigns_480x480.png?v=1600875899"></p>
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>#generalfunnel</s:tag>
    <s:tag>bestseller</s:tag>
    <s:tag>collagen</s:tag>
    <s:tag>dairy-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>gluten-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>keto-friendly</s:tag>
    <s:tag>non-gmo</s:tag>
    <s:tag>paleo-friendly</s:tag>
    <s:tag>shipping_international</s:tag>
    <s:tag>soy-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-default</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-disabled</s:tag>
    <s:tag>trending</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/2608979116145</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">45.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>CSPPDRK1</s:sku>
      <s:grams>590</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/2059602395249</id>
    <published>2018-12-20T12:30:43-05:00</published>
    <updated>2018-12-20T12:30:43-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://drkellyann.com/products/21-day-bone-broth-bundle-classic-chicken"/>
    <title>10 Box Bone Broth Bundle &amp; Save</title>
    <s:type>Soups &amp; Broths</s:type>
    <s:vendor>DISK</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/Bone_Broth_-_Classic_Chicken_10_box_bundle_1.png?v=1744209720"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>DISK<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Soups &amp; Broths<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            276.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div class="s-description">
<h2>21-Day Bone Broth Bundle</h2>
<p>If you decided to do Dr. Kellyann's Bone Broth Diet you've come to the right place to get all the bone broth you'll need for your 21-day transformation.</p>
<h2>All the nutrition, none of the work.</h2>
</div>
<p>Dr. Kellyann’s Bone Broth takes all the hard work and guesswork out of getting the collagen-packed protein and nutrients you need to nourish your body, control hunger cravings, and even help smooth away wrinkles — without any cooking or prepping so you can breeze through your 21 days!<br></p>
<p>I want your journey toward a healthier lifestyle to be on YOUR terms. I want you to look and feel your best whenever and wherever you want. And my anytime/anywhere single-servings of collagen-rich bone broth are the easiest (and tastiest) way to get there.</p>
<p><span>Consuming 1-2 packets of Dr. Kellyann's Bone Broth per day aids in supporting gut health and is ideal for intermittent fasting, GLP-1 diets, and weight loss programs. It's rich in nutrients, contains 0 sugar, and is high in protein, making it great for diabetics, seniors, and those on carnivore or paleo diets. This delicious bone broth is excellent for recovery, boosting immunity, and supporting skin, hair and nail health.</span></p>
<p><span>We suggest trying it as a savory satisfying snack when fasting, a meal accompaniment, or as a wholesome soup base in your favorite recipes.</span><span class="c-message__edited_label" dir="ltr" data-sk="tooltip_parent" aria-describedby="sk-tooltip-135077" delay="300"> </span></p>
<div class="s-description">
<span style="color: #ff2a00;" data-mce-style="color: #ff2a00;"></span>This 21-Day Bone Broth Diet product bundle gives you all the bone broth you’ll need to be successful on your 21-Day Bone Broth Diet.<br><br>
<p>This bundle includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>10 boxes of Collagen Broth <meta charset="UTF-8"> <span data-mce-fragment="1">—</span> that's 70 packets of convenient bone broth to-go! </li>
</ul>
<h3>Bone Broth Benefits</h3>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">+ 16g of protein per serving<br data-mce-fragment="1">+ Only 70 calories and less than 1g of carbs<span> </span><br data-mce-fragment="1">+ Just 230mg of sodium per serving<br data-mce-fragment="1">+ No fat / No sugar / No cholesterol<br>+ Cage-free chicken<br>+ Slow-simmered for 8 hours<br>+ Includes 7 individual packets<br>+ Just add hot water and serve! </p>
<h3><b>Anytime, Anywhere Bone Broth</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Directions: Pour contents into bowl and add 8-12 oz. of boiling water. Stir until blended. Add your favorite spices for added flavor.</span></p>
<h3><b>How Can Bone Broth Support Your Health?</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When animal bones are slow-cooked, the marrow and connective tissues release health-supporting nutrients like vitamins, minerals, and collagen-packed protein. When you go through our 21-day plan, you can see benefits in many areas of your overall wellness.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These can include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Weight loss</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Skin, joint, and bone health</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hydration</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Digestion</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Metabolism</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sleep health</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The extra protein in the broth may give you more control over your appetite and reduce hunger cravings in between meals by keeping you feeling fuller for longer. The extra protein can also play a key role in helping you maintain muscle mass and support healthy blood sugar levels. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The animal bones also contain gelatin. When our bodies digest gelatin, it is deconstructed into amino acids like glycine, glutamine, and proline. These amino acids are then sent out to wherever the body needs them. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amino acids are the building blocks of proteins and can help support digestive health, natural collagen production, and a healthy metabolism. Glutamine and glycine can also help support the gut lining and your gut microbiome, which can, in turn, support your overall health.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our bone broths are full of supportive nutrients like:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Collagen</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vitamin D</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vitamin A </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vitamin K </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fatty acids</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Iron</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Zinc</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Phosphorus</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Calcium </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Potassium </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Magnesium </span></li>
</ul>
<p><b>Encourages Healthy Weight Loss</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bone broth is low in carbs, sugar, and calories, so it makes sense that, for many, it can help curb cravings and support weight loss goals. The benefits of losing weight are felt on the inside and the outside. When you start to look great, you may start to feel great, too!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You can easily incorporate Dr. Kellyann’s bone broth by substituting bone broth for caffeinated or sugary drinks, throwing one of our on-the-go packets in your gym bag, or using it as a base for your favorite soup. And of course, you can embark on our bone broth diet plan.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By drinking two servings of Dr. Kellyann’s delicious bone broth every day, you can get an extra 32 ounces of protein into your diet, which can help you feel fuller for longer. You can also combine the benefits of bone broth with diet methods like intermittent fasting and low-carb diets.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just make sure to save your cup of bone broth for a non-fasting day, as bone broth can break a fast.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you start replacing foods that are high in sugar and carbohydrates with clean foods that are high in protein, you can burn more calories and support your metabolism. The results can be amazing!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Plus, our beef and chicken bone broths work with both keto and paleo diets. And, while there are plenty of bone broth recipes that feature non-starchy vegetables and healthy fats (while avoiding artificial sweeteners or legumes),we prefer to enjoy bone broth as-is.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After all, when you’re drinking Dr. Kellyann Petrucci’s high-quality, grass-fed chicken or beef bone broth, why add anything at all?</span></p>
<p><b>Supports Younger-Looking Skin</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not only can the bone broth diet support your weight loss journey, but the collagen contained in each serving can help support skin health, as well. Unfortunately, one fact of life is that, as we age, our natural ability to produce collagen can diminish. This can even start as early as our 20s.   </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When collagen production starts to decline, that’s when we begin to notice things like sagging skin, hallowed areas around our eyes, and fine lines and wrinkles. The good news is that you can add some collagen back to your body by drinking bone broth.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over time, you may see improvements in the tone and texture of your skin. It may even help smoothen the appearance of cellulite. </span></p>
<p><b>Promotes Gut Health</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bone broth can also play an important role in your gut health. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The gut is also sometimes called the body’s second brain. It’s no wonder, then, that a happy gut can contribute to a happier state of being. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The nutrients, proteins, and amino acids contained in bone broth can help coat the lining of your gut and support healthy digestion. Specifically, the amino acids glutamine and glycine both play vital roles in the digestive system. </span></p>
<h3><b>How Else Can You Use Bone Broth?</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The gut is the epicenter of the body, and a healthy gut can support your overall wellness — so it’s time to start taking gut health seriously. A great way to take advantage of the benefits of bone broth is by using it as part of a detox to support your microbiome.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Try using Dr. Kellyann’s 5-Day-Cleanse &amp; Reset Kit to get harmful bacteria and toxins in check. This cleansing meal plan includes some of Dr. Kellyann’s favorite cleansing foods like Lemon Sips, Chocolate or Vanilla Super Smoothies, Super Berry Smoothies, and our Lemon Chicken Soup.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By pressing the restart button with a bone broth cleanse, you may be able to minimize uncomfortable bloating, digestive discomfort, and even skin concerns. The minerals and nutrients contained in bone broth can support your gut, while collagen can help you lose that stubborn belly fat.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fortunately, bone broth can fit in a wide range of diets. Those who are on a gluten-free or keto diet should be able to incorporate bone broth into their diet easily. Simply add some veggies, and you have a nutritious and diet-friendly soup that can help you feel full and look amazing.</span></p>
<p><span size="1" style="font-size: xx-small;" data-mce-style="font-size: xx-small;">California Prop 65 Warning</span></p>
<p><span size="1" style="font-size: xx-small;" data-mce-style="font-size: xx-small;"><meta charset="utf-8"> <img data-mce-fragment="1" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461" alt="" data-mce-src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461"> WARNING: Consuming the bone broth in this product can expose you to chemicals including lead which is known to the State of California to cause cancer and birth defects or other reproductive harm. For more information go to<span> </span><a href="http://www.p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food" target="_blank">p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food</a>.</span></p>
<div>✝<em>These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.</em>
</div>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p><!-- split --></p>
<p><img height="331" width="331" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/Bone_Broth_-_Nutrition_Facts-_CC.png?v=1723643951" alt=""></p>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>badge:trending</s:tag>
    <s:tag>bestseller</s:tag>
    <s:tag>bonebroth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>dairy-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>gluten-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>healthier_2019</s:tag>
    <s:tag>keto-friendly</s:tag>
    <s:tag>non-gmo</s:tag>
    <s:tag>paleo-friendly</s:tag>
    <s:tag>shipping_international</s:tag>
    <s:tag>soy-free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-default</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-disabled</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/2059602395249</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">276.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>CBDRK10-B</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/1945191252081</id>
    <published>2018-11-21T20:27:29-05:00</published>
    <updated>2018-11-21T20:27:29-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://drkellyann.com/products/collagen-fiber-bar-in-chocolate-coconut"/>
    <title>Collagen Fiber Bars</title>
    <s:type>SLIM Bar</s:type>
    <s:vendor>DISK</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/dka_Fiberbar_Box_12count_051225a.png?v=1747075402"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>DISK<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>SLIM Bar<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            35.00 - 67.00
            <a href="https://drkellyann.com/products/collagen-fiber-bar-in-chocolate-coconut">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><h2 class="s-title">12 creamy coconut-filled bars covered with rich dark chocolate come in every box!<br>
</h2>
<ul>
<li>12 grams of fiber</li>
<li>3 grams net carbs</li>
<li>4 grams of collagen</li>
<li>Metabolic Nutrition</li>
<li>Non-GMO<br>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Want to lose weight, reduce your body fat, stay “regular,” and keep your gut microbes happy? Then you need to get enough fiber every day. That’s 25–30 grams for women and 30–38 for men.</p>
<p>This rich, decadent bar gives you an impressive 12<span> </span>grams of fiber. And it’s the best kind of fiber: natural, soluble, prebiotic fiber that helps your body absorb key minerals, keeps your digestive system running smoothly, enhances your immune function, and makes your gut microbiome glow.</p>
<div class="p65-o">
<p>This bar is so satisfying that it keeps cravings away for hours so you stay focused. Maybe best of all, it is collagen-rich for beautiful skin!</p>
<p>12 delicious collagen fiber bars come in every box!</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-size: xx-small;" size="1">California Prop 65 Warning</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: xx-small;" size="1"><meta charset="utf-8"> <img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/files/warning_b_w_480x480.png?v=1610497461"> WARNING: Consuming the bone broth in this product can expose you to chemicals including lead which is known to the State of California to cause cancer and birth defects or other reproductive harm. For more information go to<span> </span><a href="http://www.p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food" target="_blank">p65warnings.ca.gov/products/food</a>.</span></p>
<div>✝<em>These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.</em>
</div>
<br>
<p><!-- split --></p>
<p class="p2"><b><i>Ingredients: </i></b>Coconut flakes, Chocolate coating [sugar, palm kernel oil, chicory root extract (inulin), cocoa processed with alkali (15%), emulsifier (soy lecithin), sea salt, natural vanilla flavor], Inulin (Prebiotic fiber from chicory root), Grass-fed bovine hydrolyzed collagen, Acacia, Sea salt, Stevia, Pure Vanilla Extract. <b>Contains:<span> </span></b>Milk.</p>
<div class="gmail_default"><em>Manufactured in a facility that processes milk, soy, egg, wheat, peanuts and tree nuts.</em></div>
<p class="p3"><i><br>No artificial sweeteners.</i></p>
<p> </p>
<p class="p3"><img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/7575/products/Nutrition-Label-Chocolate-Coconut-Fiber-Bar_large.png?v=1542853286"></p>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>#generalfunnel</s:tag>
    <s:tag>bestseller</s:tag>
    <s:tag>keto-friendly</s:tag>
    <s:tag>non-gmo</s:tag>
    <s:tag>paleo-friendly</s:tag>
    <s:tag>shipping_international</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-default</s:tag>
    <s:tag>spo-disabled</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/1945191252081</id>
      <title>1 BOX</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">35.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>BRFIBCOCNDRK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://drkellyann.com/products/1945191252081</id>
      <title>2 BOXES</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">67.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>BRFIBCOCNDRK02</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
